{
   "questions":[
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c1",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Chin/ese/ tea/cher",
        "correctAnswer":"Chinese teacher"
    },
      {
         "qid":"p1u1-c2",
         "questionType":"pair",
         "question":"Lea/der",
         "correctAnswer":"Leader"
      },
      {
         "qid":"p1u1-c3",
         "questionType":"pair",
         "question":"Tea/cher",
         "correctAnswer":"Teacher"
      },
      {
         "qid":"p1u1-c4",
         "questionType":"pair",
         "question":"Prin/ci/pal",
         "correctAnswer":"Principal"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c5",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Jani/tor",
        "correctAnswer":"Janitor"
      },
      {
         "qid":"p1u1-c6",
         "questionType":"pair",
         "question":"Coa/ch",
         "correctAnswer":"Coach"
      },
      {
         "qid":"p1u1-c7",
         "questionType":"pair",
         "question":"Dri/ver",
         "correctAnswer":"Driver"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c8",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Gar/den/er",
        "correctAnswer":"Gardener"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c9",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Li/bra/rian",
        "correctAnswer":"Librarian"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c10",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Eng/lish/ tea/cher",
        "correctAnswer":"English teacher"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c11",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Moni/tor",
        "correctAnswer":"Monitor"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c12",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Hel/lo",
        "correctAnswer":"Hello"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c13",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Stu/dent",
        "correctAnswer":"Student"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c14",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Good/bye",
        "correctAnswer":"Goodbye"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c15",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Pre/fect",
        "correctAnswer":"Prefect"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c16",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Fri/end",
        "correctAnswer":"Friend"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c17",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Class/mate",
        "correctAnswer":"Classmate"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c18",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"After/noon",
        "correctAnswer":"Afternoon"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c19",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Morn/ing",
        "correctAnswer":"Morning"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u1-c20",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Gre/et",
        "correctAnswer":"Greet"
      },
      {
        "qid":"p1u2-d1",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Daugh/ter",
        "correctAnswer":"Daughter"
     },
     {
        "qid":"p1u2-d2",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Ba/by",
        "correctAnswer":"Baby"
     },
     {
        "qid":"p1u2-d3",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Fa/mi/ly",
        "correctAnswer":"Family"
     },
     {
        "qid":"p1u2-d4",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Un/cle",
        "correctAnswer":"Uncle"
     },
     {
        "qid":"p1u2-d5",
        "questionType":"pair",
        "question":"Fa/ther",
        "correctAnswer":"Father"
     },
     {
       "qid":"p1u2-d6",
       "questionType":"pair",
       "question":"Au/nt",
       "correctAnswer":"Aunt"
     },
     {
       "qid":"p1u2-d7",
       "questionType":"pair",
       "question":"Sis/ter",
       "correctAnswer":"Sister"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d8",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Grand/mo/ther",
      "correctAnswer":"Grandmother"
     },
     {
       "qid":"p1u2-d9",
       "questionType":"pair",
       "question":"Tw/ins",
       "correctAnswer":"Twins"
     },
     {
       "qid":"p1u2-d10",
       "questionType":"pair",
       "question":"Child/ren",
       "correctAnswer":"Children"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d11",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Grand/fa/ther",
      "correctAnswer":"Grandfather"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d12",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Grand/chil/dren",
      "correctAnswer":"Grandchildren"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d13",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Ni/ece",
      "correctAnswer":"Niece"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d14",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Ne/phew",
      "correctAnswer":"Nephew"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d15",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Par/ents",
      "correctAnswer":"Parents"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d16",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"S/on",
      "correctAnswer":"Son"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d17",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Cou/sins",
      "correctAnswer":"Cousins"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d18",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Mo/ther",
      "correctAnswer":"Mother"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d19",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Si/blings",
      "correctAnswer":"Siblings"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u2-d20",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Bro/ther",
      "correctAnswer":"Brother"
     },
    {
      "qid":"p1u3-c1",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Sch/ool /Bag",
      "correctAnswer":"School Bag"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c2",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Boo/k",
      "correctAnswer":"Book"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c3",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"P/en",
      "correctAnswer":"Pen"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c4",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Era/ser",
      "correctAnswer":"Eraser"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c5",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Pen/cil",
      "correctAnswer":"Pencil"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c6",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Ca/se",
      "correctAnswer":"Case"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c7",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Rul/er",
      "correctAnswer":"Ruler"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c8",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Cray/ons",
      "correctAnswer":"Crayons"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c9",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Gl/ue",
      "correctAnswer":"Glue"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c10",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Stap/ler",
      "correctAnswer":"Stapler"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c11",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Scis/sors",
      "correctAnswer":"Scissors"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c12",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Note/book",
      "correctAnswer":"Notebook"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c13",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Pa/per",
      "correctAnswer":"Paper"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c14",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Bot/tle",
      "correctAnswer":"Bottle"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c15",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Lunch/box",
      "correctAnswer":"Lunchbox"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c16",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Sn/acks",
      "correctAnswer":"Snacks"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c17",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Home/work",
      "correctAnswer":"Homework"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c18",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Fol/der",
      "correctAnswer":"Folder"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c19",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"Shar/pen/er",
      "correctAnswer":"Sharpener"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p1u3-c20",
      "questionType":"picture",
      "question":"High/light/er",
      "correctAnswer":"Highlighter"
     },
     {
      "qid":"p2u1-c1",
      "questionType":"pair",
      "question":"Super/mar/ket",
      "correctAnswer":"Supermarket"
     },
     {
      "qid": "p2u1-c2",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Hos/pi/tal",
      "correctAnswer": "Hospital"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c3",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Mu/se/um",
      "correctAnswer": "Museum"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c4",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ci/ne/ma",
      "correctAnswer": "Cinema"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c5",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ba/ke/ry",
      "correctAnswer": "Bakery"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c6",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ho/me",
      "correctAnswer": "Home"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c7",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Tem/ple",
      "correctAnswer": "Temple"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c8",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Gro/ce/ry",
      "correctAnswer": "Grocery"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c9",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Re/stau/rant",
      "correctAnswer": "Restaurant"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c10",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sch/ool",
      "correctAnswer": "School"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c11",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ba/nk",
      "correctAnswer": "Bank"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c12",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Cli/nic",
      "correctAnswer": "Clinic"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c13",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Mar/ket",
      "correctAnswer": "Market"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c14",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ca/fe",
      "correctAnswer": "Cafe"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c15",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Chur/ch",
      "correctAnswer": "Church"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c16",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Post /off/ice",
      "correctAnswer": "Post office"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c17",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Po/lice /stat/ion",
      "correctAnswer": "Police station"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c18",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Fi/re /stat/ion",
      "correctAnswer": "Fire station"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c19",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sa/lon",
      "correctAnswer": "Salon"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u1-c20",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Pa/rk",
      "correctAnswer": "Park"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c1",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ga/mes",
      "correctAnswer": "Games"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c2",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Pic/nic",
      "correctAnswer": "Picnic"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c3",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sand/wich/es",
      "correctAnswer": "Sandwiches"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c4",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "S/coo/ter",
      "correctAnswer": "Scooter"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c5",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Straw/ber/ries",
      "correctAnswer": "Strawberries"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c6",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Foot/ball",
      "correctAnswer": "Football"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c7",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Dri/nk",
      "correctAnswer": "Drink"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c8",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Lit/ter",
      "correctAnswer": "Litter"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c9",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Bi/cy/cle",
      "correctAnswer": "Bicycle"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c10",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Flo/wers",
      "correctAnswer": "Flowers"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c11",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sw/ing",
      "correctAnswer": "Swing"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c12",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "See/saw",
      "correctAnswer": "Seesaw"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c13",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sl/ide",
      "correctAnswer": "Slide"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c14",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Pho/tos",
      "correctAnswer": "Photos"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c15",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Fr/is/bee",
      "correctAnswer": "Frisbee"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c16",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Bar/be/cues",
      "correctAnswer": "Barbecues"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c17",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Ca/mp/ing",
      "correctAnswer": "Camping"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c18",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Sp/it",
      "correctAnswer": "Spit"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c19",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Cl/imb",
      "correctAnswer": "Climb"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p2u2-c20",
      "questionType": "pair",
      "question": "Pa/int",
      "correctAnswer": "Paint"
    }
   ]
}
